Contacts

flaviojrjardim@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/flaviojrjardim (LinkedIn) flaviojrjardim.github.io/ (Personal)

Main Skills

Software Engineering Web Development Hybrid Apps

Languages

Portuguese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working) Creole and pidgins, based on portuguese (Native or Bilingual)

Flávio Jardim

Junior Software Developer at PRIMAVERA Business Software Solution

Braga, Portugal

Summary

I'm a young Software Engineer with experience and extensive formation in application development and software design. I'm a tech enthusiast and I also have a passion for fashion.

I think my best strengths are: determination, dedication, and responsibility. I'm always striving to bring 100% to the work that I do. Good communication and interpersonal skills. Good teamwork skills. I'm always available to help and learn. Critical thinking for problemsolving.

Main specialities: Software Engineering; Understand Software Engineering Best Practices; Ability to Analyze Complex Technical Information; Analyze, Design and Implement Database Structures; Experience with Web & Hybrid applications development, i.e., AngularJs and ECMAScript; Frontend skills, e.g., HTML5, JavaScript, CSS, Sass; UI/UX skills; Experience with Multiple Coding Languages, e.g., Java, C/C++, C#, PHP; Microsoft ASP.NET MVC, Web API; Experience Experience With Source Code and Version Repository; Previous Experience Working Within an Agile Scrum Team;

Experience

PRIMAVERA Business Software Solution

Junior Software Developer December 2018 - Present Braga, Portugal

Rose team - Product Development.

Tecnologies: C#; .NET; SQL; TS; Postman.

Junior Developer April 2018 - December 2018 (9 months)

Braga, Portugal

Project:

PRIMAVERA Developers Network.

Responsabilities:

- Code samples development for integration with GitHub;
- Interaction with development teams to placement technical content in the PRIMAVERA Developers Network;
- Dynamization of the community in forums (Internal and StackOverflow);
- Technical support.

Tecnologies: C#; .NET; SQL; WordPress; Postman.

Solo PT

Frontend Developer Intern February 2017 - June 2017 (5 months)

Porto, Portugal

Web & Hybrid Apps development.

Tecnologies: AngularJS; Angular material; Gulp; npm; git; ECMAScript 6; HTML5; SCSS.

Education

ISEP - Instituto Superior de Engenharia do Porto Licenciate Degree, Informatics Engineering